Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Maps, Series I
  - Miscellaneous Maps., 000010
    - Montana. Map Type: Forest Map Quadrangle: Beaverhead National Forest (West Half) Scale: .5 in to 1 mile Coordinates: N4430-W20 Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1970; 000906
    - Montana. Map Type: Guide Map Quadrangle: Pryor Mountaibs Scale: Coordinates: Publisher: US Dept. of the Interior Bureau of Land Management, 000900
    - Montana. Map Type: Quadrangle: Southwestern Scale: Coordinates: Publisher:, 000907
    - Montana. Map Type: Agriculture Quadrangle: Missoula Scale: Coordinates: Publisher: US Deparment of Agriculture and Forest Service, 000909
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC J-19 1: 1 000 000 Defense Mapping Agency Aerospace Center, 1969; 000943
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC P-16 1: 1 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1971; 000937
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC Q-14 1: 1 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1971; 000938
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC P-14 1: 1 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1972; 000939
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC Q-15 1: 1 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1973; 000940
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC R-12 1: 1 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1973; 000947
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC R-13 1: 100 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1973; 000949
    - Operational Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: ONC Q-13 1: 100 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1973; 000950
    - Oregon. Map Type: City Map Quadrangle: Portland Scale: Coordinates: Publisher: M.W. Publicity Limited, 000912
    - Panama Republic. Map Type: Political map Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Coordinates: Publisher: Natl Geographic Institute, 1978; 000913
    - South Dakota. Map Type: Geological Survey Quadrangle: Madison Subcrop-North Central North Dakota Scale: B/A Coordinates: Publisher: North Dakota Geological Survey, 1986; 000914
    - USAF Jet Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: JNC 4A 1:3 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1960; 000944
    - USAF Jet Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: JNC-A3N 1: 3 000 000 Defense Mapping Agency Aerospace Center, 1971; 000936
    - United States and Canada. Map Type: Railroad Map Quadrangle: Scale: Coordinates: N25-W2 Publisher: Rand, McNally &Co.'s, 1885; 000934
    - United States-Western. Map Type: Region/Geographical Quadrangle: Texas-Oregon and California Scale: Coordinates: N26-W18 Publisher: S. Augustus Mitchell, 1846; 000935
    - United States. Map Type: Map of United States territories and insular possessions Quadrangle: Western Half Scale: Coordinates: Publisher:, 1953; 000931
    - United States. Map Type: Map of United States territories and insular possessions Quadrangle: Eastern Half Scale: Coordinates: Publisher:, 1953; 000932
    - United States. Map Type: Map of United States territories and insular possessions Quadrangle: Eastern Half Scale: 1 in to 37 miles Coordinates: N21-W75 Publisher: US Dept.of the Interior Bureau of Land Management, 1953; 000933
    - United States. Map Type: Road Map Quadrangle: North Dakota Scale: Coordinates: Publisher: North Dakota State Highway Department, 1967; 000916
    - United States. Map Type: Annual Sunshine and Evaporation and Solar Radiation Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 17 000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1967; 000926
    - United States. Map Type: Monthly Sunshine Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 17 000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1968; 000921
    - United States. Map Type: Population Quadrangle: Scale: More than 1 scale Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1968; 000922
    - United States. Map Type: Water Use Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 5000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1968; 000923
    - United States. Map Type: Water Resources Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 17 000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1968; 000927
    - United States. Map Type: Physiography Quadrangle: Scale: 1:17 000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1968; 000929
    - United States. Map Type: Territorial Growth Quadrangle: Scale: Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1969; 000924
    - United States. Map Type: Population distribution Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1969; 000925
    - United States. Map Type: Vegetation Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1969; 000928
    - United States. Map Type: Congressional Districts Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1969; 000930
    - United States. Map Type: US General Reference Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Coordinates: N30-W75 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1970; 000918
    - United States. Map Type: Monthly Minimum Temperature Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 17 000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1970; 000919
    - United States. Map Type: Monthly Avg. Temp Quadrangle: Scale: 1:1 7000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1970; 000920
    - United States. Map Type: General Reference Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Coordinates: N30-W75 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1976; 000915
    - United States. Map Type: Cartographic Section Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 4 560 000 Coordinates: N24-W75 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1987; 000917
  - Topographic Maps. United States., 000003
    - California-Nevada. Quadrangle: Death Valley scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3600-W11600/100*200 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1947; 000012
    - California. Quadrangle: New York Butte scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N3630-W11745/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000011
    - Colorado. Quadrangle: Creede and Vicinity scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3750-W10654/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1912; 000018
    - Colorado. Quadrangle: Creede scale: 1:125 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3730-W10630/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1914; 000017
    - Colorado. Quadrangle: Juanita Arch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3830-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000019
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Ansonia scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000026
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Wallingford scale: 1:31680 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000020
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: New Haven scale: 1:31680 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000021
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Guilford scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7237.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000023
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: New Haven scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000028
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Ellsworth scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7322.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey. Photo revised in 1969., 1956; 000024
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Mount Carmel scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000022
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Mount Carmel scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey. Photorevised in 1972., 1967; 000025
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Branford scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey. Photo revised in 1972., 1967; 000027
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Varies scale: 1 inch to 2857 feet Latitude/Longtitude: Varies Publisher: State of CT Dept. of Environmental Protection Natural Resources Center, 1992; 000029
    - Idaho. Quadrangle: Dubois scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W11200/45 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000030
    - Maryland. Quadrangle: Washington E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3852.5-W7652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000031
    - Montana-North Dakota. Quadrangle: Glendive scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10600/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000098
    - Montana-North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ekalaka scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10600/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1958; 000097
    - Montana-North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bainville SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000095
    - Montana-North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dore scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000096
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Red Lodge scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1944; 000103
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Red Lodge/Mount Marice scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/15 and N4500-W10915/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1944; 000107
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Mount Marice scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10915/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000104
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hollenbeck Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W100900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000099
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Tolman Flat scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10907.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000100
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hunters Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000101
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hollenbeck Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000102
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hunters Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000105
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Tolman Flat scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10907.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000106
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hollenbeck Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000108
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Bridger scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1989; 000110
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Red Lodge scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W11000/30X60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1989; 000111
    - Montana-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Red Lodge scale: 1: 100 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W11000/30X60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1991; 000109
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Mt. Wallace scale: 1:62500` Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W11015/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1940; 000048
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Mt. Cowen scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4515-W11015/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1940; 000049
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Mt. Douglas scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4515-W11000/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1941; 000050
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Ennis scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4515-W11130/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000075
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Mc Leod scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4537.5-W11000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000053
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Mc Leod scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4537.5-W11000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000057
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Mc Leod scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4537.5-W11000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000058
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Grant scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W11300/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1959; 000051
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Dillon E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W11230/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1962; 000054
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Alder scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4515-W11200/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000052
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Metzel Ranch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N450735-W11207.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000056
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Sheridan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4522.5-W11207.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000061
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Black John Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000034
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Bateman Coulee NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10630/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000035
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000062
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000063
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000064
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Black John Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000065
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Bateman Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000066
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Bateman Coulee NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10630/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000067
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Hultz Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10700/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000072
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000085
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000086
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000088
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000089
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jordan NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000092
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Hansen Ranch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W11300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000055
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Medicine Lodge Peak scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W11300/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000060
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Lost Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10737.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000068
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Marsh scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10452.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000041
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Allard scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10430/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000042
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Upper Magpie Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10737.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000044
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Twin Forks Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10430/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000045
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Belle Prairie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10430/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000070
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Forest Park scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10445/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000071
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Stipek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10437.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000073
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Glendive scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10437.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000084
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Long Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000033
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Belfry scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000040
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Indian Spring scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: n4507.5-w10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000074
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Long Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10852./7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000076
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Hatcher Pass scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000077
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Wade scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000078
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Belfry scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000079
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Red Lodge East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W10907.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000080
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Long Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000081
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Wade scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000082
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Red Lodge East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4507.5-W10907.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000083
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Sawmill Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10722.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000032
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Wolfe Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10715/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000036
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Swede Ridge scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10722.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000037
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Wagon Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10707.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000038
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Harper Camp scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10700/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000090
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Chalk Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10715/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000091
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Signal Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000039
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Pleasant View scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10452.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000043
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Gilbert Creek SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10630/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000046
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Gilbert Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10630/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000047
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Kester School scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000087
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Buckskin Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10315/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1974; 000069
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Alder Gulch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W11330/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000059
    - Montana. Quadrangle: scale: N/A Latitude/Longtitude: Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000093
    - Montana. Quadrangle: scale: N/A Latitude/Longtitude: Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000094
    - New Jersey. Quadrangle: scale: 1 mile to an inch Latitude/Longtitude: N4000-W7420 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1912; 000112
    - New Mexico-Arizona. Quadrangle: Gallup scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3500-W11000/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1954; 000116
    - New Mexico; Arizona; Colorado; Utah. Quadrangle: Shiprock scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3600-W11000/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000114
    - New Mexico; Colorado. Quadrangle: Aztec scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3600-W10800/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000115
    - New Mexico. Quadrangle: Albuquerque scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3500-W10800/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000113
    - New York-Massachusetts. Quadrangle: Hancock scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4230-W7315/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000180
    - New York. Quadrangle: Ashokan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1942; 000138
    - New York. Quadrangle: West Shokan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W4715/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1942; 000140
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kerhonkson scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7415/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1942; 000143
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kingston W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1942; 000153
    - New York. Quadrangle: Lake Carmel scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1943; 000122